So, the warning signs that we are living
in the very last days are no longer
hidden. They are playing out right
before our eyes in real time. And we're
going to talk about that today, as well
as covering other news going on in the
world and clown world and comments of
the day and question of the day and
everything we do here. Uh my name is Tom
and you're watching the Watching River
channel. I'm glad you're here. I hope
you're well. Today is Tuesday, September
8th, 2026.
And as far as a live studio audience
goes, I've got a squirrel playing across
the street and I have numerous birds. So
there you go. That qualifies. Before we
get to the seriousness of our chat
today, it's always important to start
off with the word of God. I am in God's
promises for your every need. It's a
little book that contains scripture. I'm
on page 130. What to do when you are in
need of peace. Let's read some of these.
Okay. Isaiah 26:3.
You will keep him in perfect peace whose
mind is stayed on you because he trusts
in you.
John 14 verse 27. I love this verse.
Peace I leave with you. My peace I give
to you. Not as the world gives do I give
to you. Let not your heart be troubled,
neither let it be afraid.
Let's go to Philippians 4 6 and 7. be
anxious for nothing, but in everything
by prayer and supplication, let your
requests be made known to God. And the
peace of God, which surpasses all
understanding, will guard your hearts
and minds through Christ Jesus. Give me
an amen. Thank you. Let's go to Romans
5:1. Therefore, having been justified by
faith, we have peace with God through
our Lord Jesus Christ.
Isaiah 26:12.
Lord, you will establish peace for us,
for you have also done all our works in
us.
Move on over to Isaiah 55:12.
For you shall go out with joy and be led
out with peace. The mountains and the
hills shall break forth into singing
before you, and all the trees of the
field shall clap their hands. Boy, that
paints a beautiful picture, doesn't it?
Psalm 37:37,
"Mark the blameless man, and observe the
upright, for the future of that man is
peace." Aren't these great? Let's do one
more. Romans 8:6, for to be carnally
minded is death, but to be spiritually
minded is life and peace. Isn't that
beautiful? How are you guys? Let me know
in the comments. I hope you're doing
well. I hope you had a a good weekend.
I think I'm going to start here because
uh you know we're just seeing more and
more signs and the ramping up of the
technology of this world and the
wickedness of this world is what I want
to talk about. Uh this was covered over
the weekend. Open AAI's chief scientist
Yakub Bahhatsky
is warning that artificial intelligence
is advancing at a pace that could become
difficult for humans to follow and
control. You you think so Jack? You
think so? His message is not necessarily
that AI is already out of control, but
that but that the speed of development
is creating a serious challenge.
Researchers and the public may not
always understand exactly how
increasingly powerful systems reach
their decisions or how their
capabilities could change over time.
Incredible how fast this technology came
upon us. Were we even talking about this
three years ago? That was kind of at the
beginning of this, you know, when chat
GPT was released and I just cannot
believe how fast it is coming at us and
how we have no say in it at all and it's
just being pushed on everyone. You know,
even the UN can't stop it right now, but
I think they're in cahoots with it
honestly. But Pahhatsky has called for
extreme caution as companies continue
developing more advanced AI models. This
concern is that innovation may move
faster than safety research, regulation,
and our ability to properly test these
systems. His comments add to a broader
debate over whether AI companies should
slow down, introduce stronger
safeguards. That ain't going to happen.
You know, it ain't going to happen. And
make sure humans remain meaningfully
meaningfully in control.
It ain't going to happen. They are just
going for it. We all know it. We're
watching it right before I they're going
for it. Nobody's slowing this down. The
central warning is simple. AI may be
improving faster than our ability to
understand and manage it. That makes
transparency, safety testing, and
responsible oversight increasingly
important as these systems become more
powerful. There you go. That says it
all. You know, we can't put the brakes
on this. Do you think we can? Let me
know in the comments. I don't see it. I
just because I don't see anyone who has
the authority and power saying stop
this. And you know the governments of
the world, they're all in on it because
they all think if we lose the AI race,
we lose. Remember what they said a few
years ago, whoever wins the AI race
rules the world. They told us, you know,
there ain't no way government's going to
back off on this. I believe we are
seeing the final touches of the beast
system that will be used during the
seven-year tribulation. We're watching
it right now. We are waiting for Jesus
right now. Day by day, we're in the very
last days. I truly believe that. I
wouldn't tell you that if I didn't truly
believe it. We are waiting right now for
Jesus. I think he could come at any time
to rapture his church.
Then we got this. End times headlines
covered this. This will show you the
wickedness of where we're headed in this
world. Okay. Parents, be warned. Disney
is preparing to introduce a new
generation of children to a world of
witches, warlocks, covens, vampires, and
supernatural magic. Sounds like great
family entertainment, doesn't it?
Disney's upcoming series Coven Academy
follows teenage witches and warlocks
attending an elite magic boarding school
in New Orleans.
Disney itself describes the series as
involving volatile magic, supernatural
conflict, and young witches learning to
master their powers. The series
premieres October 1st on free on Free
Form and begins streaming October 2nd on
Disney Plus and Hulu.
Now 1 Million Moms is sounding the
alarm, warning parents that the program
is being marketed toward younger
audiences and calling on families to
reject it. The organization argues that
Disney continues to normalize
witchcraft, sorcery, and occult themes
for children and teenagers. It's because
that's always the target. Our kids are
always the target, and we are living in
the last days. And we have seen
horrendous things pointed at our
children since CO horrendous things. And
it's getting worse and worse. But don't
don't lose heart because Jesus is still
in control. He is still on the throne.
Then we got this. You guys have been
reading about this, right? How churches
are randomly being burned around this
world and they never seem to find out
who's doing it. I saw this on rapture
ready.com. Oh, look. Yet another church
goes up in flames. Another week, another
historic church reduced to smoke and
rubble. The former St. Agnes church in
Toledo, Ohio went up in flames early on
Saturday morning. It's 116year-old
landmark steeple. It came down. The roof
burned out. Nearby homes were evacuated.
Once again, the cause is list as
currently it's listed as currently
unknown.
You think that has anything to do with
Satan's time here? his short time
because he knows time is short and he he
knows it more than a lot of believers
know it. And somebody's burning down
churches, you know, doesn't freak me out
because you know what? We are the
church. You know, the people that belong
to the Lord. It's not a brick and
mortar. It's not a building. But still,
it's amazing to see what's happening in
these last days. Then this, my goodness,
did you guys see this over the weekend?
I hadn't heard about this viral thing
about this duct tape man. you know, a
man who was so unruly in an airplane
that they had to duct tape him to the
seat. They used zip ties and duct tape
to get him to stay still. And they kept
talking about this unnamed passenger
that he tried to strangle. It turned out
it was Pastor Jonathan Khan. A lot of
you know who he is. He's written the
dragon prophecies. A a lot of stuff. It
was him. And you know what? He was
talking to that guy about Jesus. And
that guy was had a demonic spirit. And
it was just really I guess yesterday I
saw the part of the video yesterday
Jonathan Khan released a video talking
about every detail of what went on in
that plane and that was a demonic
attack. That was a demonic attack. It
was incredible you know and the
mainstream media so far they are not
talking about this being a demonic
attack obviously and they're not talking
about the fact that it was Jonathan Khan
you know this famous pastor. But
incredible times we're living in. Satan
knows time is short and we do too. Time
is short.
Then we got this. We're going to start
covering a little bit of the Middle East
news. The Financial Times reported this
blew my mind. Navy Seal divers spent
four months conducting a covert mine
clearing operation in the straight of
Hormuz. I was wondering when President
Trump said that the mines had been
cleared. I'm like, how did they pull
that off?
They did it mostly under the cover of
darkness. The mission involved rubber
boats, robotic vessels, and underwater
systems. While US Navy mind sweepers
remained outside the area, while ship
owners believe the southern shipping
route had been cleared, they doubt the
entire straight is mine free. But
alongside the divers, unmanned vessels
and specialized underwater systems were
deployed in the hazardous strait.
The inherently complex and dangerous
work of neutralizing the mines was
carried out underwater and in darkness
with the aim of removing one of the main
factors that has deterred ships from
crossing through the straight of Hermuz
since February. So it was the Navy
Seals. Does that surprise you? They're
so amazing, man. Those seals, they're
amazing. But that's how it happened.
Then we got Oh, doggy. There's a cute
doggy walking by the front of my car.
Very cute.
Sorry.
I get distracted by dogs and cats and
squirrels and birds. I I try my best to
keep my focus, but you know.
Also, Oman evacuates 16 seaman from a
Saudi vessel hit in a deadly Iranian
attack. This happened over the weekend.
Uh, the Aramco oil facility was attacked
by the Houthis in southern Saudi Arabia.
Did you hear about that? This happened
yesterday. Houthi rebels launched
multiple attacks into southern Saudi
Arabia Saturday, including one on a
facility run by oil company Aramco in
Jazan. Uh the Saudiled coalition
fighting the rebels in Yemen said in a
statement quoted by the Saudi press
agency, the coalition said that four
drones had been launched into the region
which is regularly targeted by Houthi
drone and missile attacks. There was no
loss of life, it said as well as the
Aramco facility, the rebels also hit a
desalination plant in Al Shak. So there
you go. That happened in in Saudi Arabia
over the weekend.
Then it was announced that Prime
Minister Benjamin Netanyahu will address
the UN General Assembly
uh during their annual general debate in
New York on September 24th. You wonder
if what the mayor said there, Mom
Donnie, he said that he may arrest
Netanyahu when he comes to New York. And
then President Trump said, "You will not
arrest him when he comes to New York."
We are living in interesting days, you
know. We just have a incredible time
period right now to be looking for Jesus
as we're just seeing all these things
getting into place and just looking
like, yeah, the seven-year tribulation
could begin at any time. I truly believe
it could begin any time. And I think
that starts obviously after the rapture
of the church.
You guys need to pause the video right
now. Might be a good time. Go get a
snack. Bring it back. I don't want a
snack today. I don't have an appetite
today. So, just get yourself a snack and
come back.
Iran says improved ballistic missile
shows it will take preemptive action
against threats. Iran state media early
this morning said a ballistic missile
with improved capabilities was
demonstrating a new doctrine. Thrron
will take any action against any threat
even before it is carried out.
The report by Iran's state news agency
repeatedly cited comments aired on state
TV the day before by the head of Iran's
Supreme National Security Council uh
Rosi who boasted of new missile
capability and claimed it had been
tested against a US warship but it was
not clear whether that was tested was
the missile the new report described the
solidfueled
Cassmbier is what they call it. Iran's
messaging in recent days has become more
assertive and Monday's report said that
the Cassm Bassier marks a turning point
in Iran's defense strategy. It described
the missile as having greater range and
accuracy and a half a ton warhead. The
missile was unveiled last year when it
was described as having at least a 1200
km or 745 mile range. So, they got a new
toy they're going to play with and
they're just basically, you know,
bragging about their their new toys. You
know, lot of noise around here today.
Then we got this from Bubba Bubba News
on Telegram. The IDF's own channel, own
official channel, just released the
summary of Breaking Dawn 2.0, the chief
of staff's surprise exercise testing
readiness for a sudden multiffront war
scenario.
They did this what on Saturday I
believe.
Bubba said, "I find this remarkable and
maybe even prophetic. Israel is not
preparing to go fight somewhere else far
away. Every scenario they're training
for happens right here on their own
borders in their own land. I believe
that scripture already tells us this.
The battle won't come to Israel because
Israel goes looking for it. It comes to
Israel because the surrounding nations
bring it to her doorstep. exactly as
Psalm 83 and Zechariah 12 describe. I'm
watching this closely and it's because
Israel's own military knows that
something is up, that something has
already been written. Bubba said, "Yes,
it has." Amen. Yeah. And that war could
begin at any time because they're both
threatening preemptive strikes. Israel's
threatening Iran. Iran and the proxies
are threatening Israel. And I think
prophetic wars are coming.
Then this broke. Uh, the Assad era
government in Syria was constructing a
nuclear reactor that was configured to
produce fistal material for possible use
in nuclear weapons. The head of the IAEA
said this morning early, "The
configuration and the technical features
of the nuclear reactor under
construction in Syria during the
leadership of ousted former President
Assad were very efficient in the
production of fistal material that could
be directly used for the fabrication of
nuclear weapons," the IAEA director,
General Rafael Gross said. So there you
go.
Then we got this. We'll file this in the
rumors of war category. This was from
insider paper. Japan scrambled fighter
jets for five straight days following
Chinese reconnaissance aircraft flights
off the country's southwestern islands
in the East China Sea, the Japanese
Defense Ministry's Joint Chief of Staff
said this morning on Monday. So there
you go. Uh rumors of war, they're all
over the place. Uh Russia on Monday
early this morning ordered the German
consulate in St. Petersburg to be shut,
giving diplomats until September 18th to
leave the country and demanding the
employees of Germany's Gerta Institute
which is closed last week exit by the
end of the week. Lot of rumors of war in
these last days.
Also, Russia said it has developed an AI
powered radar system capable of
identifying any flying target, including
Twinkies. No, I added that for humor,
but not not Twinkies, but yeah, any
flying target, you know. There you go.
I'm going to do one more from end times
headlines.
Americans are already feeling the pain
every time they walk into a grocery
store. But now there's another growing
concern beyond the price tag. How safe
is the food we're bringing home? The
average American household is now
spending more than $10,000 a year on
groceries. While prices have reportedly
risen more than 18% since 2022.
Meanwhile, thousands of products have
been recalled this year, and the FDA
recently reached a record 19
simultaneous outbreak investigations
involving everything from infant formula
to produce. Yeah, you can't even trust
the produce, the meat, you know,
everything. You know what? You trust
Jesus. You know, that's what I do when I
buy groceries cuz what are you going to
do? You know, you got to eat. You know,
food safety advocates are also raising
alarms over reduced staffing and fewer
inspections across federal agencies.
They should take care of that quick
because we really should have, you know,
safe food, wouldn't you think, you know,
but we're living in clown world. So,
earthquakes. This is probably one of the
lowest earthquake numbers I've seen
since I started this channel. In the
last 24 hours, there were 36 over 4.0
and only eight over 5.0. That is low.
You know what that means? They're
probably going to be huge in the next
couple days.
All right, it's time for our question of
the day.
What's your favorite New [clears throat]
Testament letter?
Of all the letters in the New Testament,
what's your favorite? Mine, and I'm
going to say today because it's going to
change, you know, and my pastor right
now is going through Galatians, but I'm
going to say Galatians because right now
I've been reading it over and over
again, and it's just grace, grace,
grace, grace, grace. I love Galatians.
But what's your favorite New Testament
letter? Let me know in the comments. All
right, these comment these questions of
the day have just been amazing because
you guys are blessing each other. I just
see it. It's beautiful.
All right, guess what?
It's time for Clown World. Let's go.
Okay, this was in Tech Spot.
Humanoid robots are being prepared for
combat as China moves them from labs to
military training grounds. Didn't I
always tell you this? I've told you this
for years. Back when humanoid robots
could barely stumble forward without
falling over, there were plenty of jokes
about their use on the battlefield,
Terminator style, not being a much of a
concern. Now though, these machines are
running faster than the fastest human
and doing parkour and China wants them
to turn them into robotic military
combatants.
August saw the World Humanoid Robot
Games take place in China where robots
took part in several events. The same
month, Unitry claimed its Superman robot
can run faster than Usain Bolt, although
the figure has not been independently
verified.
Reuters reported that two days after the
games ended, the People Liberation
Army's official newspaper, the PLA
Daily, called for researchers to
accelerate the transfer of these
technologies from laboratories to
military training grounds. They want to
fight wars with these humanoid robots.
Reuters reviewed more than 100 Chinese
military pro procurement notices,
academic studies, patents, official
publications, government records, and
defense company materials. It found that
the country is accelerating research
into the robotics military uses and
planning for their eventual wartime
deployment.
>> [music]
>> I'm sorry, that was kind of dramatic.
And you know, I just had to add some
dramatic music because we're living in
Crown World, you know. It was kind of
dramatic. No. Yeah. I I don't worry
about China's military humanoid robots
because I have an appointment with Jesus
as most of you do and it's it's coming
very soon.
But there you go. You're caught up.
That's everything going on. I think now
we will read a few comments of the day.
My question of the day yesterday was
what scripture is the most comforting to
you? And uh some of these comments talk
about it. This is Kmac.
This scripture literally saved my life.
Proverbs 3:5. Trust in the Lord and lean
with all your heart and lean not on your
own understanding. Acknowledge him in
all your ways and he will make straight
your paths before you. Amen. Amen.
Kayak. Wow. It literally saved your
life. I'd like to hear that story. It's
a great testimony. I bet.
Juny, this might be a weird comfort
verse, but the very short verse, Jesus
wept. I find it such a comfort in my
most horrific times to know Jesus knows
exactly what that pain feels like. I'm
never alone in my weeping. It's
beautiful, Judy. Thank you. Berean
woman, my go-to verse. For God has not
given us a spirit of fear, but of power
and of love and of a sound mind. And
that's 2 Timothy 1:7.
Deborah, whosoever believeth in me shall
have eternal life.
Kathy, I will never leave you nor
forsake you.
Maria, comforting verse, he will wipe
every tear from their eyes. There will
be no more death or mourning or crying
or pain. For the old order of things has
passed away. Revelation 21:4.
Amen, Sister Rob. Luke 22 28. And when
these things begin to come to pass, then
look up and lift up your heads for your
redemption drawth nigh. Amen, brother.
Amen. Aren't these great? You get so
encouraged by these scriptures. Plan
1956 said, "Many times I get overly
anxious about the traumatic era in which
we live, but this verse helps to keep me
things in perspective." Psalm 46:10, "Be
still and know that I am God. I will be
exalted among the nations. I will be
exalted in the earth." Many many of you
shared that verse. Um
Psalm 46:10. Yeah, beautiful. Cray
Philippians 4:13. Greater is he that is
in me than he that is in the world.
Amen. Let's do one more. D. Peace I
leave you. My peace I give to you. Not
as the world gives do I give to you. Let
not your heart be troubled, neither let
it be afraid. John 14:27 which I read
earlier in the video. Yeah, that is
comforting D. Thank you. Beautiful,
beautiful comments of the day. You guys,
you know what? We are living in the last
days. Most of us know we are. And we are
waiting for Jesus right now to come and
rapture his church in a pre-tribulation
rapture. We're not trying to guess the
day or the hour. We just know we're in
that season. So, we're waiting. But do
you know Jesus? Do you know what God did
2,000 years ago? He sent his only
begotten son that whoever believes in
him in Jesus will not perish, won't go
to hell, but will have everlasting life,
eternal life. That's what God did. He
sent Jesus here. And Jesus came here,
the lamb of God, slain from the
foundation of the world. Jesus came to
this world from heaven to die in that
cross. Why? Because each one of us, you
and me and every one of us, we need a
rescue. Because we're all sinners. We
fall short of the glory of God. We miss
the mark and we need a rescue. And God
provided a rescue. And Jesus came here
to die on that cross to shed that blood.
Because you know what? That blood that
Jesus shed is the once-forall payment
for sin. Once you have faith in that
blood and understand that you're a s
sinner that needs payment for your sins
and that payment is blood. Why is it
blood? Because the most high God is so
offended by sin. It has to be a serious
serious payment. It's blood. But Jesus
shed that blood that once we say to him,
Jesus I understand I'm a sinner and I
can't pay for these sins of my own. If I
shed my own blood, it wouldn't save a
squirrel. But Jesus, I believe in the
blood you shed, that it was shed to wash
these sins away, to wash me white as
snow. And I am believing that. I am
having faith in your blood that it will
do that. And at that moment, your sins
will be washed away. And you will be
washed white as snow. And you say,
"Jesus, I believe in your finished work
on the cross. You got nailed to the
cross. You shed that precious blood. You
died. You were buried. And you rose
again the third day. You are the one and
only savior of the world and I am in
dire need of a savior. So from now on I
am yours. And you know what? At that
moment of belief in the atoning blood of
Jesus and in his finished work on the
cross, guess what? You're saved. You are
saved. You are sealed until the day of
redemption, you're born again. Because
at that moment, God will place the Holy
Spirit in you. This is miraculous stuff
I am talking about. God doesn't want
anyone to perish, but that all should
come to repentance, and he provided the
blood payment to rescue us. What are you
going to do with that? Can you seriously
listen to that and go, "Well, I don't
want that." I mean, I get when people
say, "I just don't know how to believe
that." I've had there was a friend of
mine for many years who said, "It all
sounds so good. I just can't believe it.
I just just not in me. I can't believe
it." You know, I'm I'm the one who runs
like where's the line for him? And and
thank God there's no line. It's just
believing in the everlasting gospel and
in his atoning blood. You could have new
life. Jesus wants to spend forever and
ever with you. And he paid your way with
his blood. He paid for your sins and my
sins with his blood. You know, don't be
one of the ones who just keeps putting
this off forever because one day you
will take your last breath and if you
don't believe in the atoning blood of
Jesus and in the gospel, you are going
to face him on judgment day and he's
going to say, "Away from me. I never
knew you." And I'm telling you,
there will not be a more terrifying
moment in your entire existence. And you
will know I am kneeling in the presence
of God. You will know there will be no
question then. And then you will be led
off to eternal separation from God. I
don't like talking about hell. I really
don't. But you won't say you're unfair
because you'll say, "No, I heard the
gospel. I remember that guy in the car
telling me the gospel that my sins have
been paid for by the blood of the lamb,
the lamb of God, Jesus." And I said,
"No, I don't want that. I'm fine. I'll
take my chances. Please don't do that."
Okay? In my prayer time this morning, I
said a prayer for you because I prayed
for every single person who would watch
this video. So that includes you. So,
like it or not, you have been prayed
for. And if we're not raptured today,
and I think today is a perfectly good
day for the rapture, but if not, God
willing, I will see you guys tomorrow. I
love you guys.
>> Oh, Jesus, [music]
Savior,
master, [music]
creator.
You're the alpha. [music]
Omega,
you're the King of Kings.